Guide to the Locus Science Fiction Foundation archives, 1942-2012 RL.11689
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Name Files
  - Sheffield, Charles, 1981-1984 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (three letters), book cover for "My Brother's Keeper"
  - Shelukhin, Vladmir V., 1985-1989 (Box 5)
  - Shepard, Lucius, 1987 (Box 5)
    Clipping, promotional materials
  - Sherred, T.L., 1985 (Box 5)
  - Shibano, Takumi, 1983-1994 (Box 5)
  - Shiel, M. P., undated (Box 5)
    Information about books for sale
  - Shiner, Lewis, 1987 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), editorial from Charles Platt
  - Shirley, John, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Sibley, Don, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Siegel, Jan, undated (Box 5)
  - Siegel, Jerry, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Silverberg, Robert, undated (Box 5)
  - Simak, Clifford, 1981-1988 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (four letters), obituaries
  - Simmons, Dan, 1992-2002 (Box 5)
    Invitation, clippings
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis, 1983-1991 (Box 5)
    "Publishers Weekly" interview, obituaries
  - Singh, Kirpal, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Siodmak, Curt, undated (Box 5)
    "Filmfax" interview
  - Skipp, John, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Sladek, John, 1989 (Box 5)
    Interview in "Tales of the Unanticipated"
  - Slesar, Henry, 2002 (Box 5)
    Obituary, clippings
  - Slonczewski, Joan, undated (Box 5)
  - Smiley, Jane, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Smith, Clark Ashton, 1985-2003 (Box 5)
    Memorial service program, press release, obituaries
  - Smith, George O., undated (Box 5)
    Obituaries, profile written by Frederik Pohl
  - Smith, Guy N., 1982 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), two book covers, Black Hill Books catalog
  - Smith, Mark and Julia, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Smith, Michael Marshall, 1996 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), interview
  - Smith, Ron, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Smith, Wilbur, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Sohl, Jerry, 1983-1987 (Box 5)
  - Somtow, Sucharitkul Papinian, 1985-1998 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, promotional materials, clippings
  - Spencer, William Browning, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Sperry, Ralph A., 1982 (Box 5)
  - Spencer Library (Kansas), 1984 (Box 5)
    Clippings, description of the collection
  - Spinrad, Norman, 1981-1999 (Box 5)
    Open letter, clippings, press release, excerpt from autobiography
  - Springer, Nancy, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Springer, Sherwood, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Spruill, Steven, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Stableford, Brian, 1979-1991 (Box 5)
  - Stallman, Robert, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), obituary, author information sheet
  - Stanislaw, Lem, 1979-2002 (Box 5)
  - Stapledon, Olaf, 2007 (Box 5)
    Profile in "Steam Engine Time"
  - Stark, Ben J., 1984-1986 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, lawsuit documents
  - Stasheff, Christopher, undated (Box 5)
  - Stephenson, Neal, 1991-2008 (Box 5)
    Clippings, interviews
  - Sterling, Bruce, 1989-1999 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), clippings
  - Sternbach, Rick, undated (Box 5)
    Book cover for "Hell Spark"
  - Stevens, Arce, James, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Stewart, George R., 1979-1980 (Box 5)
    Clippings, obituary
  - Stewart, Mary, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Stine, Hank, undated (Box 5)
  - Stine, R. L., 1995-2008 (Box 5)
  - Stolbov, Bruce, 1987 (Box 5)
    Synopsis of "Last Fall"
  - Stone, Susan, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Straub, Peter, 1983-2003 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (two letters), clippings, flyer
  - Strete, Craig, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Strieber, Whitley, 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Stross, Charles, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
    Clipping, interview
  - Stroud, Jonathan, 2003 (Box 5)
    "Publishers Weekly" ad
  - Strugatsky, Arkady, 1981-1986 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter from John Costello with interview of Boris Strugatsky), promotional materials, clippings
  - Stublarec, Jim, 1979 (Box 5)
    "A Marketing Approach to Science Fiction" essay
  - Sturgeon, Theodore, 1971-1985 (Box 5)
    Remembrances written by Betty Ballantine, Isaac Asimov, Robert Heinlein, Laurence M. Janifer, Samuel R. Delany, Ann C. Crispin, Greg Bear, Spider Robinson, David Gerrold, Somtow Sucharitkul, and Frank M. Robinson, "West Wind" No. 95, copies of "You: A Talk by Theodore Sturgeon," Institute for the Study of Consciousness event information, book cover for "Slow Sculpture," Introduction of "Roadside Picnic"
  - Suckling, Nigel, 2000 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (two brief letters from Marianne Plumridge)
  - Sullivan, Tim, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Sullivan, Tricia, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Swain, Dwight V., 1992 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter, poem, and remembrance from Joye R. Swain), funeral program
  - Swisher, Robert D., 1976 (Box 5)
  - Tabakow, Lou, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Taine, John, 1991 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter from Constance Reid), resume
  - Tall, Stephen (Compton Crook), undated (Box 5)
  - Taylor, G.P., undated (Box 5)
  - Taylor, L.A., 1994 (Box 5)
    Bio and text from online message board
  - Tennant, Emma, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Tepper, Sherri S., 1997 (Box 5)
  - Trevis, Walter, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), promotional materials, clippings
  - Thomas, Elizabeth Marshall, undated (Box 5)
  - Thomas, Ross, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Thompson, Don and Maggie, 1994 (Box 5)
    Bio, obituary
  - Thompson, Earl, 1967 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (three letters), "Untitled APA-L Zine"
  - Thyme, 1983 (Box 5)
    "Thyme" number 28
  - Tilley, Patrick, undated (Box 5)
  - Tiptree, James, Jr., 1972-1996 (Box 6)
    Correspondence, clippings, news of her death, bio
  - Tofte, Arthur, 1977-1980 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), obituary
  - Thomsen, Brian, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Trimble, Bjo and John, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Tron, Walt Disney Productions, 1982 (Box 6)
  - TSR, 1993 (Box 6)
    "Twenty Years of TSR" promotional materials
  - Tubbs, E.L., 1981 (Box 6)
  - Tucker, Wilson "Bob", 1983-2003 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief letter from Wilson, short email from James Knappenberger), two copies of "The Best of Wilson Tucker" book cover
  - Turner, George, 1979-1991 (Box 6)
    Correspondence, clippings, interview
  - Turtledove, Harry, 1979-1992 (Box 6)
  - Tuten, Frederic, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Tuttle, Lisa, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Tyers, Kathy, 1987 (Box 6)
    "Firebird" book cover
  - Tymm, Marshall, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Updike, John, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Vallejo, Boris, undated (Box 6)
  - Van Allsburg, Chris, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Vance, Jack, 1988 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one letter), clippings, promotional materials
  - Van Der Poorten, Alfred, 1982-1987 (Box 6)
  - Van Vogt, A.E., 1980-1986 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one letter), IDS newsletter
  - Varley, John, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (two letters), "Some of Life's Little Digressions," interview
  - Vicinanza, Ralph, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Vidal, Gore, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Vinge, Joan D., undated (Box 6)
  - Vollman, William T., 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Volsky, Paula, undated (Box 6)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1973-1997 (Box 6)
  - Vos Post, Jonathan, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Wagner, Karl Edward, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Waldrop, Howard, 1987-2007 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief email), two copies of "Nova Express" 1987
  - Wandrei, Donald, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Wangerin, Walter, Jr., 1987 (Box 6)
  - Watson, Ian, 1981-1999 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (three letters), clipping
  - Watt-Evans, Lawrence, undated (Box 6)
  - Waugh, Sylvia, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Weil, Ellen, undated (Box 6)
    "An Extended Family" essay
  - Weininger, Gail, 2005 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one card)
  - Weis, Margaret, 1987-2004 (Box 6)
  - Wellman, Manly Wade, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    Obituaries, one photograph
  - Wells, H. G., 1996 (Box 6)
  - Wenguang, Zheng, undated (Box 6)
    "The Writing Way and Works Searching" essay
  - Wentworth, K. D., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Wertham, Frederic, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Westlake, Donald E., undated (Box 6)
  - Westall, Robert, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Wharton, William, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Wheelan, Michael, 1980-1985 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one postcard and birth announcement from Wheelan, one letter from his attorney)
  - White, E. B., 1985 (Box 6)
  - White, Ted, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - Whittemore, Ed, 1983-1987 (Box 6)
  - Wibberley, Leonard, undated (Box 6)
    Obituary, clipping
  - Wilder, Cherry, 1977-1984 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (three letters), "Witches in the West" script
  - Wilhelm, Kate, 1979-1983 (Box 6)
    Promotional materials, clipping
  - Willard, Nancy, 1988-1992 (Box 6)
  - Williams, Kit, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Williams, Michael Lindsay, 1986 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one letter with promotional materials)
  - Williams, Robert Moore, undated (Box 6)
  - Williams, Tad, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Williams, Walter Jon, 1998 (Box 6)
    One holiday card
  - Williamson, Jack, 1972-2005 (Box 6)
    Correspondence, promotional materials, event information
  - Willis, Connie, 2009 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (holiday card with family letter)
  - Wilson, Daniel H., 2010 (Box 6)
  - Wilson, Gahan, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Wilson, Richard, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Wilson, Robert C., 2001 (Box 6)
  - Wind, David M., 1987 (Box 6)
  - Wizards of the Coast, 2001 (Box 6)
    "Salon" article by John Tynes
  - Wodehouse, P.G., undated (Box 6)
  - Wollheim, Donald A., 1942-1979 (Box 6)
    Interview, press release, one photograph
  - Wolner, Rena, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
  - Wolfe, Gene, 1972-2014 (Box 6)
  - Womeck, Jack, 1994-1998 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), promotional materials
  - Wood, Bridget, undated (Box 6)
  - Wood, Susan, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Woods, Lebbeus, 1983 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one letter from Byron Preiss)
  - Wood, Wallace, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Wren, M.K., 1978-1988 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one letter), promotional materials, clipping
  - Wright, S. Fowler, 1996 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (email from grandson)
  - Wu, Dingbo, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
  - Wu, William, 1985 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (clipping)
  - Xingshi, Liu, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Xiao, Yang, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Yamashita, Karen Tei, undated (Box 6)
  - Yan, Wu, 1997 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one partial letter)
  - Yarbro, Chelsea Quinn, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Yerka, Jacek, undated (Box 6)
  - Yonglie, Ye, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    Bio, correspondence, SF news from China, one photograph
  - Young, Robert F., 1978-1986 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief letter from Young, two letters from Russell Galen), promotional materials
  - Zacharius, Walter, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Zavgorodny, Boris, 1989 (Box 6)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), "'The Oversan' -- a New Amateur Fantastic Magazine in the USSR" report written by Andrew Lubensky
  - Zebrowski, George, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Zelazny, Roger, 1967-1984 (Box 6)
    Correspondence, photographic negatives, "Burnt-Out Case" speech, interview
  - Zipes, Jack, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Zuber, Bernie, 1992 (Box 6)